<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects | R-Ladies Colombo</title>
    <link>/project/</link>
      <atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Projects</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/img/R-Ladiesdisplayname.png</url>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/project/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>JOIN US!</title>
      <link>/project/join-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/join-us/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;R-Ladies is a worldwide organization whose mission is to promote gender diversity in the R community via meetups, colloborations and mentorship in a friendly and safe environment. There are 140+ R-Ladies chapters worldwide and R-Ladies Colombo is the first ever chapter in Sri Lanka.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;R-Ladies Colombo welcomes anyone with an interest in R, whether you’re a newbiew, aspiring R user or an experienced R programmer. All you have to do is to provide, create and maintain a safe, friendly and welcoming environment where all members can interact and enjoy the benefit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-can-you-contribute&#34;&gt;How can you contribute?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Give a talk at a future meetup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead/organize a hackathon or a collaborative coding activity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Suggest  Meetup topics or event ideas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start/lead a study group&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recommend a speaker, tutorial or other resource&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write a blog post&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Live tweet at our Meetups and events&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to solve issues on our GitHub page&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out our upcoming events on our &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.meetup.com/rladies-colombo/&#34;&gt;meetup&lt;/a&gt; page.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STUDY GROUPS</title>
      <link>/project/study-group/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/study-group/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Study groups meet separately at their own designated times to talk about R-related topics and to promote the use of R.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would like to start or lead a Study Group contact us at colombo@rladies.org and we will offer guidelines and assistance.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SUPPORT US!</title>
      <link>/project/support-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/project/support-us/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are always looking for organizations to support our monthly Meetups! Specifically, we look for companies or organizations that can host us in their space and/or provide food and drink for Meetup attendees.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
