<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors | R-Ladies Colombo</title>
    <link>/authors/</link>
      <atom:link href="/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Authors</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/img/R-Ladiesdisplayname.png</url>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>/authors/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;welcome-to-r-ladies-colombo&#34;&gt;Welcome to R-Ladies Colombo!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;div&gt;
    This site is still under development.
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;R-Ladies is a worldwide organization whose mission is to promote diversity in the R community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;R-Ladies Colombo chapter is a part of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://rladies.org/about-us/&#34;&gt;R-Ladies Global&lt;/a&gt; community with the aim of building a colloboraitve network of R enthusiasts, newbies, learners and  experts to facilitate individual and collective progress while achieving proportionate representation by encouraging, inspiring, and empowering people of genders currently underrepresented in the R community via meetups, mentorship &amp;amp; global collaboration!. There are 140+ R-Ladies chapters worldwide and R-Ladies Colombo is the first ever chapter in Sri Lanka. As a founding principle, there is no cost or charge to participate in any of our R-Ladies chapter events. To ensure a safe, enjoyable, and friendly experience for everyone who participates, we follow the &lt;a href=&#34;https://rladies.org/code-of-conduct/&#34;&gt;R-Ladies International Code of Conduct.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out our upcoming events on our &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.meetup.com/pro/rladies&#34;&gt;meetup&lt;/a&gt; page and links to the associated resources on &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/rladiescolombo&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt; and visit us on &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/RLadiesGlobal&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt; for regular updates!.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would like present at R-Ladies Colombo or have an idea for an event you would like us to organise (eg: R workshops, career panels, networking events, and talks from package developers), get in contact via twitter XXX or email us at XXX.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information about R-Ladies Global, visit &lt;a href=&#34;https://rladies.org/&#34;&gt;rladies.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robert Ford</title>
      <link>/authors/robert-ford/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/authors/robert-ford/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
