<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors | R-Ladies Colombo</title>
    <link>/authors/</link>
      <atom:link href="/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Authors</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/img/R-Ladiesdisplayname.png</url>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>/authors/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;welcome-to-r-ladies-colombo&#34;&gt;Welcome to R-Ladies Colombo!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;R-Ladies Colombo is a local chapter of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.rladies.org&#34;&gt;R-Ladies Global&lt;/a&gt;, an organisation that promotes diversity in the R community worldwide. We meetup in person or virtually to learn about the R programming language, algorithms and advanced tools.  There are 177 R-Ladies chapters worldwide and R-Ladies Colombo is the first ever chapter in Sri Lanka.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;R-Ladies welcomes members of all R proficiency levels, whether you&amp;rsquo;re a new or aspiring R user, or an experienced R programmer interested in mentoring, networking &amp;amp; expert upskilling. Our community is designed to develop our members&amp;rsquo; R skills &amp;amp; knowledge through social, collaborative learning &amp;amp; sharing. Supporting minority identity access to STEM skills &amp;amp; careers, the Free Software Movement, and contributing to the global R community!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a founding principle, there is no cost or charge to participate in any of our R-Ladies communities around the world. Check out our upcoming events on our &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.meetup.com/rladies-colombo/&#34;&gt;meetup&lt;/a&gt; page. You can access our presentations, R scripts, and projects on our &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/rladiescolombo&#34;&gt;Github account&lt;/a&gt; and follow us on &lt;a href=&#34;https://twaitter.com/RLadiesColombo&#34;&gt;twitter&lt;/a&gt; to stay up to date about R-Ladies news!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To ensure a safe, enjoyable, and friendly experience for everyone who participates, we follow the  &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/rladies/starter-kit/wiki/Code-of-Conduct&#34;&gt;R-Ladies International Code of Conduct&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/rladies/starter-kit/blob/master/RLadiesRulesAndGuideLinesENES.md&#34;&gt;community guidelines&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would like present at R-Ladies Colombo or have an idea for an event you would like us to organize (eg: R workshops, career panels, networking events, and talks from package developers, get in contact via twitter &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/RLadiesColombo&#34;&gt;@RLadiesColombo&lt;/a&gt; or email us at &lt;a href=&#34;https://rladiescolombo.netlify.com/#demo_home&#34;&gt;colombo@rladies.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information about R-Ladies Global, visit &lt;a href=&#34;https://rladies.org/&#34;&gt;rladies.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robert Ford</title>
      <link>/authors/robert-ford/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/authors/robert-ford/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
